We are sorry.
We...
will get married.
(Episode 10)
Thank you.
Drive safely.
Yoon Jun Seo.
That was for Shin Yu Mi.
That was for your parents.
There is nothing for me.
Han Tae Seok.
If it had been something I could give up,
I wouldn't have done it.
I wouldn't have done it this way.
Eun Seo and I can't be apart.
Even if we hurt all of you,
we can't give up on ourselves.
We can't, Tae Seok.
Mom, I can't help it.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I... Jun Seo...
You can't say that. That's wrong, Eun Seo.
That's wrong.
Eun Seo.
I want you to be with them as a family...
and be loved the way
you were loved before.
I want to see you live like that.
That's what you can do for me.
I understand why you love your brother.
But that's not love.
It's just because
you've been apart for a long time.
It's all I want.
This is all I want from you.
Could you do that for me?
I wasn't a great mother to you,
but I'm still your mom.
So please listen to me.
Eun Seo, you have to stop this.
Stop now, Eun Seo.
Stop this, Eun Seo.
Hello.
Is this Eun Seo?
Where are you, Eun Seo?
You don't look good.
What?
It's nothing.
How was it with you?
I was scolded.
How are Mom and Dad?
How is Yu Mi?
We...
You need only think about me.
You needn't worry about anything else.
I won't.
You'll try to be happy.
I will.
But...
Why am I so anxious?
I absolve you from your sins.
You're finally here.
You're finally here,
but just for cleaning.
Do I mean that little to you?
I was going to call you.
Were you?
So when?
When were you going to call?
When you and Jun Seo get married?
I'm sorry.
You're not sorry.
You're not someone who would feel sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop saying you're sorry.
What exactly are you sorry for?
Are you sorry for betraying me
and running away?
Or...
are you sorry for using me
when you don't love me?
Or...
are you just saying you're sorry
because you don't know...
how to break up with me?
Haven't you ever loved me,
not even for a little bit?
Not even a little?
No. I have not.
I haven't loved you,
not even for a moment.
I have not loved you.
I have never loved you.
Eun Seo.
Let's meet.
Please come meet me right now.
I love you, Eun Seo.
I love you.
I don't care about anything else.
Just...
let me see you.
How can you do this to me?
Get out, Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Please come out.
Please meet with me.
Why are you hurting him?
Why are you hurting so many people?
I'm sorry.
Don't forgive me.
Please don't forgive me.
I came here to pick up my belongings.
My painting tools and everything
I left here,
all the memories with you, and...
my heart that I gave to you,
I'll take everything back.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I get it now. I can understand.
I think it's the same.
If what you feel for Eun Seo is...
the same as what I feel for you,
I can understand.
That is why you can't leave her.
If you have that feeling,
you can't help it.
There is no need to be sorry.
I found out you could have this feeling.
I've never imagined
you could have this feeling.
But I was wrong.
Because your feeling isn't meant for me,
it took a long time for me
to accept the fact.
I'll get punished later.
But so be it,
there is no option for me other than this.
I'm sorry, Yu Mi.
You don't need to be sorry.
There's an easy way to put it in words.
I just realized.
We're not meant to be together.
You'll find someone great.
I know. I'm a good person.
Yes.
Can you help me move things?
Drive safely.
Thanks.
Can you give me a hug for the last time?
This is your scent...
and the feeling of being in your arms.
I'll remember it.
Please be happy.
You have to be happy.
This...
What is it?
Mom brought me too much kimchi.
This isn't for Jun Seo,
but for Ji Hwan, right?
No, what are you talking about?
Okay, I will take it.
- Give me a minute
- Okay.
Dad.
Are you here for Sin Ae?
No.
Sin Ae was off today.
Why?
Because your mother...
is sick.
Is she sick?
Is Mom sick?
Does it look bad? Is it okay?
It's good. Do as you want.
It'll be a great piece as it is.
I don't think it looks good.
I will do it again.
That one looks bad.
You are here.
- Yes, I came to hang out.
- I see.
Where is Eun Seo?
Her father came to the hotel.
Did something happen at home?
You came.
Why are you sick?
Why?
Is it because of Jun Seo and me?
No.
It's not.
It's not because of you.
Mom...
Why would I...
Why would I be sick because of you?
Eun Seo.
It is our fault.
It is our fault. It's on your dad and me.
We made you and Jun Seo part terribly,
so things turned out this way.
You missed each other so much,
so you feel this way now.
I've been thinking.
Why don't you study more?
In the U.S. or in Europe...
I want to send you anywhere you want.
Let's go together.
I am sorry.
Eun Seo.
Yes.
Your mother and I have never...
had a day going by
without thinking of you.
We are sorry.
Don't be, Dad.
Whether biologically related or not,
you're my daughter.
I've never forgotten that.
I was always grateful
that you and Jun Seo...
got along with each other
without a single argument.
But now, you and Jun Seo are...
I am sorry.
Let's go to the U.S.
Three of us go together, and...
you'll meet a good man and get married.
She will marry me.
She's getting married to me.
If she goes to the U.S.,
she'll go there with me.
Eun Seo will stay with me from now on.
You...
You are siblings.
There is no way
a sister can get married to her brother.
When I told you
Eun Seo was my only sister,
you told me she wasn't.
You said she wasn't my sister anymore.
Then why are you telling me
I can't love her?
You left her here for ten years
because she wasn't my sister.
You...
Dad.
We're not siblings.
We're not related,
and we're in love.
So, what is the matter?
What is?
We're getting married
with or without your permission.
You...
Dad.
Jun Seo.
You're not my son anymore.
You're not my son.
Even if you cut me off,
it won't change anything.
We're getting married.
I won't leave her...
as I was forced to do before.
Everything is a mess, isn't it?
It's not.
What is a mess?
You had an argument with Dad,
and Mom is sick.
You and I...
hurt Yu Mi and Tae Seok.
Eun Seo, think about it this way.
We have been through everything.
We've dealt with everything we had to,
and now we have only each other.
No.
We did wrong.
We shouldn't have done it,
although we forgive ourselves.
Stop.
What should we do now?
It's all my fault.
It's all because of me.
If you hadn't met me...
If I hadn't met Mom and Dad,
all of us would have been happy.
Don't make me get upset.
If you hadn't loved me...
I was so happy to meet you.
I've never thought of...
being happy without you.
Me, neither.
I haven't...
I haven't thought of that, either.
Give me that.
How can you be worse than me?
- Like this.
- Give it to me.
How about going to the farm this weekend?
Are you suggesting we run away again?
There's no one to stop us anymore.
I just...
I wished we could stay longer last time.
Eun Seo.
Why don't we live there?
What is it?
It's nothing.
Will you go to the farm with me?
Yes.
I promise.
Hello.
Is this Yu Mi's mother?
Yes.
What did you say?
Ma'am.
You are bad.
You are bad and mean.
Is she alive?
Is she still alive?
Ma'am.
Who is Shin Yu Mi's family?
Is she okay?
Is my daughter going to be okay?
Yes.
She will be fine,
but she is very weak
since she was in shock.
Also, her right arm
would be fine for daily use,
but there's a chance that...
No, no way.
My daughter is a painter.
This can't be happening. Doctor sir, no.
Can I see her now?
Can I meet her?
How dare you see her?
Whom do you want to meet?
Ma'am.
Who made her like that?
Whose fault is this?
Whose fault?
Whose...
(Emergency)
Excuse me. Which room is Shin Yu Mi in?
Her family doesn't want any visitors.
Please let me see her just for a moment.
- Your room looks great.
- Yes.
Is this a kitchen?
Yes, go ahead.
You are lucky to be the son of the CEO.
The bedroom is upstairs.
You can look around.
Okay.
Tae Seok.
Tae Seok?
You have quite a few men you call by name,
don't you?
It's fine, Choi Eun Seo.
You can live the way you live.
I'll live the way I do.
I'm so sorry.
You're sorry?
But there's nothing I can do for you.
I don't accept apologies.
Rather, I might get back at you,
so stay out of my sight.
Tae Seok.
Yes, I'm coming.
I will leave now, sir.
Tae Seok!
Okay, I said I'm coming.
Yu Mi.
Are you all right?
You were worried.
You were worried about me.
I am sorry.
I didn't intend to make you worried.
I have no luck with anything.
Why did you do that?
I just...
- I'm sorry.
- I am sorry.
I wanted to go there.
The beach where you drew me
for the first time.
If I go there,
I feel like you'd be there
just like you were at that time.
I wanted to go.
I'm sorry.
What can I do?
What would you have me do?
What can you do for me?
What can you do?
I'm not sure if I can go back
to my normal life.
I can't even work.
What can you do for me?
I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
I'll be fine, so go. Just go.
I won't bother you.
Please don't care about me and,
be happy with Eun Seo.
I'm sick of everything.
I'm not going to see you again.
I feel terrible for you
to see me like this.
Do not come back.
I will come back tomorrow.
Did you meet Yu Mi?
Eun Seo.
I see.
Is she all right?
Is she in pain?
She's fine.
That's good. I'm relieved.
But she's probably depressed,
because she can't paint anymore.
Jun Seo.
Yes?
Do you remember our plan
for going to the farm tomorrow?
I do.
We can't go, can we?
That's disappointing.
You're sorry, aren't you?
It's all right if you can't go.
I'm telling you this in case you feel bad.
I should get going.
I made you dinner.
Don't forget to eat.
Eun Seo.
Let's go. We'll go tomorrow.
I don't want to apologize to you.
We keep apologizing to everyone.
I don't want to apologize to you,
at least.
We'll go there tomorrow.
All right?
We'll go.
We'll go there.
Yes, hello.
Jun Seo, Yu Mi is not here.
- She is gone.
- What?
Ma'am.
Jun Seo.
What should we do?
Where did she go?
I wanted to go there.
The beach where you drew me
for the first time.
Yu Mi.
- Let me go!
- Yu Mi!
- Don't do this.
- Please don't!
- Let me go!
Don't do this to me!
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me! I'll kill myself!
Promise me you won't leave me!
Don't leave me!
Why are you not answering, Eun Seo?
Please call me back, okay?
Jun Seo.
I was scared that you had gone.
Go back to sleep.
Will you stay?
I don't care if you think I'm pathetic.
Please stay.
Please don't leave me.
I won't.
I won't leave you.
I won't go anywhere.
Eun Seo.
I don't think I can make it.
I can't come.
So, don't wait for me.
I'm so sorry.
Are you sure you want to stay here?
Do you like it here?
Yes, Jun Seo.
I have a favor to ask you.
Hello.
Jun Seo.
I look terrible.
This...
might be the last time.
Does she want to meet me?
Yes.
I am sorry, Eun Seo.
I am so sorry, Eun Seo.
I didn't mean it, but...
It is okay.
But...
I don't think I can live without Jun Seo.
Even if I lose everything...
Even if...
Get well soon, Yu Mi.
Jun Seo will never leave you.
I am sorry for everything.
I am sorry.
Jun Seo, I'm leaving.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
I'm sorry.
You told me you didn't want to
say sorry to me.
But you say that so often.
Make Yu Mi happy.
Eun Seo.
Then, I will be happy.
All right, then.
Eun Seo.
If I were to hold your hand,
I won't be able to let go of it.
I absolve you from your sins.
Jun Seo, good bye.
Good bye.